[
  {
    "front": "はじめまして",
    "back": "처음 뵙겠습니다"
  },
  {
    "front": "お元気ですか？",
    "back": "잘 지내세요?"
  },
  {
    "front": "久しぶり",
    "back": "오랜만이에요"
  },
  {
    "front": "すみません",
    "back": "실례합니다 / 죄송합니다"
  },
  {
    "front": "お願いします",
    "back": "부탁합니다"
  },
  {
    "front": "行ってきます",
    "back": "다녀오겠습니다"
  },
  {
    "front": "行ってらっしゃい",
    "back": "다녀오세요"
  },
  {
    "front": "ただいま",
    "back": "다녀왔습니다"
  },
  {
    "front": "おかえりなさい",
    "back": "어서 오세요"
  },
  {
    "front": "お疲れ様です",
    "back": "수고하셨어요"
  }
]